(Sheldon:)I went to the FBI
and retracted my statement.
(Howard:)And they were okay with that?
(Sheldon:)No. If anything,
I made it worse.
(Sheldon:)In any case, I have
been riddled with guilt,
(Sheldon:)which is causing
Gorn-infested REM sleep.
(Sheldon:)So, I'm here now
to say I'm sorry.
(Howard:)Are you kidding me?
(Howard:)You've set my career back
at least two years,
(Howard:)and you think you can make it
right with "I'm sorry"?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)I followed the social protocol.
(Sheldon:)I attempted to right the wrong,
and when I failed to do so,
(Sheldon:)I delivered a heartfelt apology.
(Sheldon:)Now you say,
"Apology accepted,"
(Sheldon:)and I will offer you
a one-time-only high five.
(Howard:)Your apology is not accepted.
(Sheldon:)You're tricking me.
(Sheldon:)It really is, isn't it?
(Howard:)Leave me alone, Sheldon.
(Dr Tyson:)Dr. Cooper, I just
wanted you to know
(Dr Tyson:)I'm sorry for the role I
played in the Pluto matter.
(Sheldon:)Oh, shut up.